https://www.techsoft.com/privacy-statement/

About UsServices & Solutions
IT Services
Managed ServicesOffice 365 Migration and DeploymentTechnology Planning and ConsultingIT Support
Cyber Security Services
Security AuditsSecurity Testing & EvaluationPCI Compliance and AuditingSecurity Policy and Procedure Development
Process EngineeringEngineering Support Services
Software Development & DesignDatabase Development & SupportSystems IntegrationWeb DevelopmentIndependent Verification & Validation (IV & V)Technical DocumentationTesting & Evaluation
Training Services
Training ApproachInstructor Led TrainingTraining SystemsWeb Based TrainingMobile Application Training
Multimedia Services
News & EventsCareersContact UsEmployee Portal
Privacy Statement
At TECHSOFT, we understand the concerns of users visiting www.TECHSOFT.com (“Site”). TECHSOFT respects your privacy and treats the information you provide us, including your Personal Information, with care. This Privacy Statement applies to our Site. It explains how we collect, use, and disclose information collected from you and the rights and choices available to you. View our Site’s Terms and Conditions.
This Privacy Statement does not apply to information collected from you offline, to TECHSOFT websites not linked to this Privacy Statement or to third party websites linked to our Site. Your use of TECHSOFT’s websites which do link to this Privacy Statement is subject to this Privacy Statement and its related Terms of Use. Your use of third party websites is governed by their respective privacy policy.
Personal and Other Information
Through your interaction and use of our Site, TECHSOFT may collect “Personal Information”, which is information that identifies or relates to an individual. As examples, Personal Information may include your name, physical address, telephone number, e-mail address, company affiliation, and associated interests.
TECHSOFT may also collect “Other Information” through your interaction with and use of the Site, which is not directly related to an individual. As examples, Other Information may include browser and device information, data collected through automated electronic interactions, application usage data, demographic information, geographic or geo-location information, and statistical or aggregated data.
Statistical or aggregated data does not directly identify a specify person, but it may be derived from Personal Information. For example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of users in a particular zip code.
In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information. In such cases, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information.
Information You Provide to Us
If you request or provide Personal Information through our Site using our online contact forms, we store the Personal Information you provide to assist us in responding to your requests. If you apply for a job at TECHSOFT, the Personal information we receive from you is used for employment consideration and other human resource purposes, such as communicating with you in writing, by telephone, or online; evaluating your application; analyzing our staffing needs and practices; or supporting other actions related to our hiring process and employee administration. We may combine your data with research tools and information from other sources. Unless you request otherwise, we may keep your Personal Information for future consideration. If you provide Personal Information through links to third party websites, you may be asked to provide additional information by these websites.
Information We Collect by Automated Tools
When you access our Site, we may collect Other Information by automated means, including the use of cookies, web server logs, and third party analytics. Cookies are small pieces of data or data files that are sent by a website to your web browser and stored on your computer. They are used to understand general traffic patterns on our Site. The Other Information stored in the cookie is used for statistical tracking and other purposes, but not for individual identification. Cookies are also used to prefill forms so that you do not need to re-enter the data, such as when you apply for a job online. Accepting a cookie does not give us access to your computer or any Personal Information about you. We may use the aggregated data to provide feedback to our web designers, content providers, or business managers to assist them in improving our Site and services offered. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser.
If you select this setting, however, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site. Additionally, our web servers may log Other Information such as your device type, operating system type, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. We may also record Other Information such as the address of the webpage that referred you to our Site and the IP address of the device you use to connect to our Site. Additionally, we may log Other Information about your interaction with our Site, such as pages you visit. Because we do not track our Site’s users over time and across third-party websites, we do not respond to browser “do not track” signals at this time. We may also use third party web analytics to help us analyze how users engage with our Site. The Other Information collected will be disclosed to, or collected by, these third party service providers.
How We Use Your Personal Information
In accordance with applicable laws, TECHSOFT may use your Personal and Other Information for the purposes listed below:
to send you information you requested or “opted-in” to receive
to evaluate your qualifications for employment and contact you, as appropriate, for employment opportunities
to support human resource functions including employee administration and analysis of hiring and recruitment processes
to identify, prevent, and protect against cyber security and other security events, espionage, fraud, unlawful activity, claims, and other liabilities
to comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements and standards consistent with industry practices and our policies
Information We Share
Although TECHSOFT does not sell, rent, or loan your Personal or Other Information to any third party, we may disclose such information as listed below:
if required by law or through a legal process
when formally requested by law enforcement authorities or other government entities
when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent harm or financial loss
in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual espionage, cyber security or security events, or other fraudulent or illegal activity
any other legal purpose
We also reserve the right to transfer Personal Information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business and assets.
Online Recruiting Information
We may collect online recruiting information from individuals who visit our Site and are interested in pursuing job opportunities with TECHSOFT. To this end, our Site may provide you with the opportunity to review and apply for available positions listed in an online jobs database and provide assistance to individuals needing a disability reasonable accommodation.
If you choose to proceed and gain access to this database through our Site, you will be linked to a third party website hosted and maintained by one or more of our service providers (“Online Recruiting Site”). The Online Recruiting Site will allow you to provide information (e.g., your CV, contact information and identification of TECHSOFT positions of interest) that will be shared with TECHSOFT and used to evaluate your eligibility for employment and contact you as appropriate. Please note that third party vendors may be responsible for operating the Online Recruiting Site, and their privacy practices may be different than TECHSOFT’s. We encourage you to review such privacy policies and terms of use posted on the Online Recruiting Site prior to submitting any Personal Information in connection with your employment application.
Privacy of Children
TECHSOFT does not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 on the Site. We do not knowingly allow children to communicate with us or use any of our online services. If you are a parent and become aware that your child has provided us with information, please contact us as provided below.
How We Protect Personal Information
While TECHSOFT is committed to protecting your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, we cannot fully eliminate all security risks. TECHSOFT maintains safeguards to protect Personal Information, but we cannot guarantee security.
Changes to Privacy Statement
TECHSOFT reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time with or without notice, and we recommend you visit this page frequently to determine if any changes have occurred. You can determine when this Privacy Statement was last revised by referring to the “Effective Date” at the top of this page. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will become effective upon posting on this Site.
Links to Other Websites
This Privacy Statement applies only to our Site. You should be aware that through links you may be directed to other websites that we do not control. TECHSOFT has no control over the privacy notices, policies or practices of these other websites, and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites to which we link, list, rank or identify by means of a search. TECHSOFT takes no responsibility for the products, services, policies, or actions of third parties or the content of third party websites. When you leave our Site and go to a third party website, we encourage you to read the privacy policies and other notices posted.
Your Rights and Choices
At our Site, you can sign up to receive TECHSOFT Email Alerts for information that interests you, such as the latest TECHSOFT news and publications, as well as investor information including SEC filings, daily stock quotes, and more. We offer “opt-in” lists so you can sign up and sign off at any time. To unsubscribe, simply reply to the email address on the bottom of every email we send you.
